{"Name":"영어 문제집 (문장)","Problems":[{"Question":"She is my ___.\r\n:그분은 내 엄마야.\r\n1.mom\r\n2.dad\r\n3.son","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"He is my ___.\r\n:그분은 내 아빠야.\r\n1.mom\r\n2.dad\r\n3.son","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"He is my ___.\r\n:그는 내 아들이야.\r\n1.mom\r\n2.dad\r\n3.son","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"He is my _______.\r\n:그는 내 형이야.\r\n1.brother\r\n2.sister\r\n3.baby","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"She is my ______.\r\n:그녀는 내 언니야.\r\n1.brother\r\n2.sister\r\n3.baby","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"He is my ____.\r\n:그는 내 아기야.\r\n1.brother\r\n2.sister\r\n3.baby","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"She is my ____.\r\n:그녀는 내 아내야.\r\n1.wife\r\n2.husband\r\n3.daughter","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"He is my _______.\r\n:그는 내 남편이야.\r\n1.wife\r\n2.husband\r\n3.daughter","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"She is my ________.\r\n:그 아이는 내 딸이야.\r\n1.wife\r\n2.husband\r\n3.daughter","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"They are my _______.\r\n:그분들은 내 부모님이야.\r\n1.parents\r\n2.father\r\n3.mother","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"He is my ______.\r\n:그분은 내 아버지야.\r\n1.parents\r\n2.father\r\n3.mother","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"She is my ______.\r\n:그분은 내 어머니야.\r\n1.parents\r\n2.father\r\n3.mother","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"He is my _____.\r\n:그분은 나의 삼촌이야.\r\n1.uncle\r\n2.aunt\r\n3.grandfather","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"She is my ____.\r\n:그분은 나의 이모야.\r\n1.uncle\r\n2.aunt\r\n3.grandfather","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"He is my ___________.\r\n:그분은 나의 할아버지야.\r\n1.uncle\r\n2.aunt\r\n3.grandfather","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"She is my ___________.\r\n:그분은 나의 할머니야.\r\n1.grandmother\r\n2.family\r\n3.niece","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"They are my ______.\r\n:그들은 나의 가족이야.\r\n1.grandmother\r\n2.family\r\n3.niece","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"She is my _____.\r\n:그녀는 나의 여자조카야.\r\n1.grandmother\r\n2.family\r\n3.niece","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"He is my ______.\r\n:그는 나의 남자조카야.\r\n1.nephew\r\n2.cousin\r\n3.mom","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"She is my ______.\r\n:그는 나의 남자조카야.\r\n1.nephew\r\n2.cousin\r\n3.mom","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"I'm in the _____.\r\n:난 집에 있어.\r\n1.garden\r\n2.kitchen\r\n3.house","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"I'm in the ______.\r\n:난 정원에 있어.\r\n1.garden\r\n2.kitchen\r\n3.house","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"I'm in the _______.\r\n:난 정원에 있어.\r\n1.garden\r\n2.kitchen\r\n3.house","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"I'm in the ______ ____.\r\n:난 거실에 있어.\r\n1.bathroom\r\n2.bedroom\r\n3.living room","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"I'm in the ________.\r\n:난 욕실에 있어.\r\n1.bathroom\r\n2.bedroom\r\n3.living room","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"I'm in the _______.\r\n:난 침실에 있어.\r\n1.bathroom\r\n2.bedroom\r\n3.living room","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"I'm in the ____.\r\n:난 마당에 있어.\r\n1.basement\r\n2.attic\r\n3.yard","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"I'm in the ________.\r\n:난 지하실에 있어.\r\n1.basement\r\n2.attic\r\n3.yard","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"I'm in the _____.\r\n:난 다락방에 있어.\r\n1.basement\r\n2.attic\r\n3.yard","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"I'm in the ______.\r\n:난 차고에 있어.\r\n1.wall\r\n2.window\r\n3.garage","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"Dad is cleaning the ____.\r\n:아빠는 벽을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.wall\r\n2.window\r\n3.garage","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"Dad is cleaning the ______.\r\n:아빠는 창문을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.wall\r\n2.window\r\n3.garage","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"Dad is cleaning the ____.\r\n:아빠는 문을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.room\r\n2.roof\r\n3.door","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"Dad is cleaning the ____.\r\n:아빠는 방을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.room\r\n2.roof\r\n3.door","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"Dad is cleaning the ____.\r\n:아빠는 지붕을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.room\r\n2.roof\r\n3.door","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"Mom is cleaning the _____.\r\n:엄마는 바닥을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.ceiling\r\n2.chimney\r\n3.floor","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"Mom is cleaning the _______.\r\n:엄마는 천장을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.ceiling\r\n2.chimney\r\n3.floor","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"Mom is cleaning the _______.\r\n:엄마는 굴뚝을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.ceiling\r\n2.chimney\r\n3.floor","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"Mom is cleaning the ______.\r\n:엄마는 계단을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.fence\r\n2.house\r\n3.stairs","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"Mom is cleaning the _____.\r\n:엄마는 담을 청소하고 계셔.\r\n1.fence\r\n2.house\r\n3.stairs","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"}]}
